

ABOUT ME

I am a Technical Project Manager with **16+ years** of experience in infrastructure services. An Al researcher with a foundation in data science, machine learning, driving the evolution of infrastructure services toward a fully automated, intelligent ecosystem

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/deb abrata-mallik-156990137

https://github.com/dmallik85

EDUCATION

B.E. in Information Science & Engineering (ISE).

V.T.U Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

DOB

15 April 1985

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Bengali

DEBABRATA MALLIK

TECHNICAL PROJECT MANAGER

Rolkata, West Bengal

&+91 8334029818

⊠debabrata.mallik@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tata Consultancy Services Pvt. Ltd.

Kolkata

January 2015 – Till date

Accenture Services Pvt. Ltd.

Kolkata

November 2013 – January 2015

Infosys BPO Ltd.

Bengaluru

January 2011 – October 2013

Aivea Software Pvt. Ltd.

Bengaluru

October 2008 – January 2011

Technical Project Manager

- Led multiple infrastructure modernization program
- Proven ability to lead projects from concept to execution
- Familiar with CI/CD tools and practices
- Proficiency in server, cloud, and virtualization architecture

IT Operations Analyst

- Skilled in L3 server administration and virtualization technologies
- Proven track record in enhancing automation
- Proficiency in server and virtualization technologies
- Implement and enforce security policies, access controls

Senior Systems Engineer

- Skilled in L2 server and data centre support
- Proven track record in incident resolution and RCA
- Administration and maintenance of file services, permission, and regular backup
- Develop and maintain scripts for software rollout

IT Support Engineer

- Responsible for L1 server administration and support
- Manage and maintain Active Directory user accounts, groups, OUs, and GPOs
- Provided technical support to internal users
- Performed end-to-end provisioning of physical servers

SKILLS

VMWARE ARCHITECTURE

PROJECT MANAGEMENT

DATA SCIENCE & ML

COMMUNICATION

SERVER ADMINISTRATION

CLOUD ADMINISTRATION

PYTHON, TERRAFORM

LEADERSHIP

CERTIFICATIONS

- AWS Certified Solution Architect
- Certified Kubernetes Administrator
- MS Certified System Administrator

TRAININGS

- Data Science, ML and AI (Pursuing)
- vSphere 6.5 ICM, optimize & scale
- Active Directory Domain Services